<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rotaract Wageningen</title>
    <link>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rotaract Wageningen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:51:12 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rotaractwageningen.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour de RAC: Rotaract Maastricht </title>
      <link>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:51:12 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>Tour de RAC is an auto-orientation tour in which about 70 vintage cars participate every year. During this event we provide a full-day program, where we give the car enthusiast a wonderful day. Through the now notorious ball-arrow system, the teams follow the route and see the beautiful places of Maastricht and surroundings.
For more information Click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twin project Timisora (Roemenie): Rotaract Utrecht</title>
      <link>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/blog/simple-post-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:39:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/blog/simple-post-title/</guid>
      <description>Over the past year, Rotaract Utrecht has entered into a partnership with Rotaract Timisoara Cosmopolitan (Romania) in the form of a twin project. Rotaract Utrecht has raised money by organizing a very successful wine tasting. As a result, a total of two sports days were organized for orphans in Timisoara, of which the first sports day took place on 1 June. After quite a few Skype sessions between both clubs, it was in October: a part of our club has traveled to Timisoara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Run: Rotaract Rivierenland</title>
      <link>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/blog/simple-image-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rotaractwageningen.nl/blog/simple-image-post/</guid>
      <description>The Santa Run is a 3 km long fun run for the whole family. All participants walk dressed as Santa Claus a simple and enjoyable course. The relatively short course makes the run very suitable for both young and old, but also for people in wheelchairs, parents with prams or owners with their dogs. The proceeds of the Santa Run 2018 go to Stichting Help Elkaar in Geldermalsen. A local goal that works with heart and soul for people who have virtually nothing to spend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>